getsatisfaction.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Get Satisfaction

## Highlights

  * When you register to participate in a community, we share your email address with our customer that established that community.
  * We may share your personal information only with other third parties who are our service providers, and only as necessary for them to provide those services. Our service providers may not use this information for any other purpose.
  * The information you post in a community is publicly available and searchable. If you post in a private community, that information is shared with all registered users of that community.  

  * If you would like to permanently delete your account, please [submit a support ticket to our team.](https://getsatisfaction.com/corp/help/submit-a-ticket/)
  * You can manage your email notifications and other profile information [here](http://getsatisfaction.com/me).  

## Introduction

Get Satisfaction provides a customer engagement platform that enables companies to build better relationships with their customers.  The communities powered by Get Satisfaction enable companies to create a public space for conversations with and among their customers.  We believe that creating an environment of trust is important to open, honest communications. 

This privacy policy describes how Get Satisfaction collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: [http://getsatisfaction.com ](http://getsatisfaction.com/)and aliased client domains. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Get Satisfaction has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and its practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements ](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.

TRUSTe’s certification applies to the Get Satisfaction Service where Get Satisfaction is the data controller while on www.getsatisfaction.com and does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software or our mobile application.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [legal@getsatisfaction.com](mailto:legal@getsatisfaction.com).   If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Get Satisfaction complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  Get Satisfaction has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Get Satisfaction’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

The use of our Services is subject to our [Terms of Service](https://getsatisfaction.com/corp/website/terms-of-service) and this Privacy Policy.  When you use our Services, you consent to our use and disclosure of your information subject to these terms.  Regardless of where you live or where you provide information to us, you authorize Get Satisfaction to use your information worldwide and to our exporting your information to the United States.  If you do not want to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and those in the Terms of Service, you should not use or access our Services.

## Definitions

We have created this Privacy Policy to let you know how we collect, use, and share information when you use our website, software, or other services (“Services”).  We are committed to keeping you informed about how we use your information.

In this Privacy Policy, we refer to the companies that establish and manage the community as our “Customers,” and we refer to the individuals who access or participate in these communities as “Users.”

Get Satisfaction communities may be moderated by our Customers that have established the community or by third parties.  Get Satisfaction communities are often embedded in our Customers’ websites or in third party sites such as Facebook pages, and may be controlled by Customers or other third parties.  Our Services also contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by Get Satisfaction.  Those websites and third party sites may have other terms and privacy policies that govern their use that are different from these terms.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party sites.  We encourage you to be aware who controls the sites that you visit and to read the privacy statements of all sites that collect personally identifiable information.

## User Registration

When you register for our Services, we collect your email address and we ask you to create a nickname to identify yourself.  We use this information to create a registration profile for each User.  You must register in order to create a topic or reply to an existing topic, but you may view information in public communities without registration.

We also support a way to log in to our Services through other social media services such as Facebook and Google.  When you log in this way, we ask you to authorize the social media service to share certain personal information with us.

In some cases, our Customers have implemented a Single Sign On registration process where the login credentials you use with the Customer’s service are shared with Get Satisfaction.

Once you have registered, you may also voluntarily provide additional information in connection with your account, such as your name and other profile information like a tagline, Twitter handle, location, or blog address.  We always display your nickname and certain profile information along with the content you contribute to the community.  You may change the information in your profile at any time, but it is always publicly accessible worldwide. 

## Collecting Information on our Website

You may also provide contact information, including your name and email address, when you interact with our website, such as by signing up for our newsletter, applying for a job, contacting sales, or initiating other transactions.

When you are on our website, we may collect personal information from you, including contact information such as your name, email address, mailing address, and phone number.   We may also collect information about your business such as company name, company size, and business type. We may use this information for a variety of purposes:

  * Fulfilling your order
  * Sending you an order confirmation
  * Assessing the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Sending you requested product or service information
  * Sending you a newsletter or other information
  * Sending you marketing communications
  * Responding to your questions and concerns
  * Improving our website and other marketing efforts
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Enabling you to post your resume, search job postings, and contact us or be contacted by us

Our website includes certain social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to enable these features to function properly.  Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website.  Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing that feature, not this privacy policy.

We display success stories of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you may contact us at [legal@getsatisfaction.com](mailto:legal@getsatisfaction.com).

## Participation in a Community

The nature of our Services is that they provide a public space to engage with other individuals.  Therefore, the information you post in a community is public and is shared with everyone, which means that it may be displayed worldwide, indexed by search engines, archived by the Customer who created the community or other third parties, and hosted on other web sites.

This includes the content you post as well as information about your content, such as when you posted it and whether others have responded to it.  All of this information may be accessible to search engines and other third party services, as well as other applications that the customer who establishes the community may use.

We believe that it is important to the integrity of a conversation to maintain the entire conversation thread, so we do not permit you to delete a post once you have submitted it.  In certain circumstances, such as if your post has not been commented on, it may be possible to alter or delete it, but since this is not always available, we ask that you carefully consider what you post before submitting it.  Instructions for deleting information you have submitted can be found in the section of this Privacy Policy entitled “Modifying or Deleting your Information and Account Settings.”

Although we recommend that our Customers and Users adhere to our Community Guidelines, our Customers are responsible for managing their communities.  Get Satisfaction is not responsible for any misuse or abuse that may be carried out by our Customers or Users, including misuse of information that you volunteer in the course of participating at the site.  However, we will work with our Customers to address issues we become aware of, so if you find offensive material or think that someone is misusing your identity, please contact us at [legal@getsatisfaction.com](mailto:legal@getsatisfaction.com).

## Sharing and Disclosure

By registering for or joining a community, you agree to allow us to share your email address with the Customer who established the community.  In some cases, you may have shared your email address with that Customer already, such as by registering for a service offered by that Customer.  That Customer’s use of your email address is subject to its privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may preserve, use, and disclose your information in the following circumstances: 

  * If we believe that it is reasonably necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding alleged illegal activities or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person
  * To investigate violations of our various terms of service
  * To comply with a law, regulation or legal request;
  * To protect the safety of any person
  * To address fraud, security or technical issues
  * To protect our rights or property

However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a request from a third party’s, including a government entity, to disclose your information.

Get Satisfaction may assign or transfer this Privacy Policy, and your User account and related information and data, in the event Get Satisfaction is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

In addition, we may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public user profile information, information you post in a community, the topics you follow, or the Users who follow topics you create.

## Notifications

We may use your contact information, including your email address, and other profile information to send you notifications, such as an email to let you know that another user has commented on a topic you have created in a community, to notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service, to send you information about our Services, or to market to you.  Our emails will include a link permitting you to unsubscribe from such email communications.

You can manage your profile information to unsubscribe from notifications and to manage the types of information you receive directly from Get Satisfaction.  You may also unsubscribe by following the instructions contained within the notification. If you are a registered user, you may manage your notifications in your profile by logging into your account settings [here](http://getsatisfaction.com/me).

## Cookies

Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services.  A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your device.  We use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most devices automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your device, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not wish to have cookies enabled, please disable them in your browser settings.  However, some Services may not function properly if you disable cookies. For information about how to delete cookies for your particular browser [click here](http://www.wikihow.com/Clear-Your-Browser's-Cookies).

A complete list of the cookies used by the Services is [here](http://getsatisfaction.com/corp/website/cookies).

## Web Beacons / Gifs

We employ, or our third party analytics and tracking vendors employ, a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), which help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. We and our third party partners also employ scripts and tags that help us better manage content on our site. We may tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information. The use of cookies, clear gifs and scripts by third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML 5 and Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

## Behavioral Targeting

We partner with third parties to manage our advertising on other sites. These third parties may use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Log Data

Our servers automatically record information (" **Log Data** ") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, search terms, and cookie information. We may link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you for the purpose of analyzing site usage and improving the user experience. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, or visit a third-party website that includes Get Satisfaction content. We use Log Data to measure, customize, and improve our Services. We retain this Log Data for one month..

## Third Party Service Providers

Get Satisfaction uses a variety of third-party service providers to help develop, provide, and improve our Services, such as hosting our platform, providing login functionality, providing analytics functionality, or supporting integration with third party applications.  We may share your information with these third parties, and these third parties may collect information from you while you are using the Services, including information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address.  We may share your private personal information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.

## Security and Information Protection

We work hard to protect the information submitted by our Customers and Users from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction.

  * We encrypt many of our Services using SSL, including our login pages.
  * We require the use of strong passwords.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to help prevent unauthorized access.

Since the transmission of information over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be completely secure, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  Also, we are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in our Services.

## Modifying or Deleting Your Information and Account Settings

If you are a registered user, you may manage the information in your profile by logging into your account settings [here](http://getsatisfaction.com/me).  If you would like to permanently delete your Get Satisfaction account or request deletion of any personally identifiable information, [submit a ticket](https://getsatisfaction.com/corp/help/submit-a-ticket/) and we will update or deactivate your account.  We will respond to your request within 30 days.

Any posts you've made in the community before the date of termination will be retained.  You understand and acknowledge that copies of information you submit may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your content.

## Data Retention

We will retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services or the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.  If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [legal@getsatisfaction.com](mailto:legal@getsatisfaction.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be available here: <http://getsatisfaction.com/corp/website/privacy-policy>.  If we make a change to this policy that is material, we will notify you via an email to the email address associated with your account or by posting a prominent notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective.  We may also notify you by posting in [our customer community](http://getsatisfaction.com/getsatisfaction) to our support community or by sending a message from our [Get Satisfaction Twitter account](https://twitter.com/getsatisfaction). By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or comments, please email us at [legal@getsatisfaction.com](mailto:legal@getsatisfaction.com) or come to our community at <https://getsatisfaction.com/getsatisfaction>.

Here is our physical mailing address:

Get Satisfaction, Inc.  
1550 Bryant Street, Suite 350  
San Francisco, California 94103

**Effective August 15, 2014**

**Older privacy policy[08/15/2013]**
